justrentalsdubai.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy Statement | Justproperty.Com | JustProperty.com

Budget

-

  * AED 0 
  * AED 20,000 
  * AED 30,000 
  * AED 40,000 
  * AED 50,000 
  * AED 60,000 
  * AED 70,000 
  * AED 80,000 
  * AED 90,000 
  * AED 100,000 
  * AED 110,000 
  * AED 120,000 
  * AED 140,000 
  * AED 160,000 
  * AED 180,000 
  * AED 200,000 
  * AED 220,000 
  * AED 250,000 
  * AED 300,000 
  * AED 350,000 
  * AED 400,000 
  * AED 500,000 
  * AED 600,000 
  * AED 700,000 

  * AED 0 
  * AED 20,000 
  * AED 30,000 
  * AED 40,000 
  * AED 50,000 
  * AED 60,000 
  * AED 70,000 
  * AED 80,000 
  * AED 90,000 
  * AED 100,000 
  * AED 110,000 
  * AED 120,000 
  * AED 140,000 
  * AED 160,000 
  * AED 180,000 
  * AED 200,000 
  * AED 220,000 
  * AED 250,000 
  * AED 300,000 
  * AED 350,000 
  * AED 400,000 
  * AED 500,000 
  * AED 600,000 
  * AED 700,000 

Alert 

Map View 

List View 

Shortlist (0) 

Area

Min - Max

  * 0 sq. ft. 
  * 500 sq. ft. 
  * 600 sq. ft. 
  * 700 sq. ft. 
  * 800 sq. ft. 
  * 900 sq. ft. 
  * 1,000 sq. ft. 
  * 1,500 sq. ft. 
  * 2,000 sq. ft. 
  * 2,500 sq. ft. 
  * 3,000 sq. ft. 
  * 3,500 sq. ft. 
  * 4,000 sq. ft. 
  * 4,500 sq. ft. 
  * 5,000 sq. ft. 
  * 5,500 sq. ft. 
  * 6,000 sq. ft. 
  * 6,500 sq. ft. 
  * 7,000 sq. ft. 
  * 7,500 sq. ft. 
  * 8,000 sq. ft. 
  * 8,500 sq. ft. 
  * 9,000 sq. ft. 
  * 9,500 sq. ft. 
  * 10,000 sq. ft. 
  * 10,500 sq. ft. 
  * 11,000 sq. ft. 
  * 11,500 sq. ft. 
  * 12,000 sq. ft. 
  * 12,500 sq. ft. 
  * 13,000 sq. ft. 
  * 13,500 sq. ft. 
  * 14,000 sq. ft. 
  * 14,500 sq. ft. 
  * 15,000 sq. ft. 
  * 15,500 sq. ft. 
  * 16,000 sq. ft. 
  * 16,500 sq. ft. 
  * 17,000 sq. ft. 
  * 17,500 sq. ft. 
  * 18,000 sq. ft. 
  * 18,500 sq. ft. 
  * 19,000 sq. ft. 
  * 19,500 sq. ft. 
  * 20,000 sq. ft. 

  * 0 sq. ft. 
  * 500 sq. ft. 
  * 600 sq. ft. 
  * 700 sq. ft. 
  * 800 sq. ft. 
  * 900 sq. ft. 
  * 1,000 sq. ft. 
  * 1,500 sq. ft. 
  * 2,000 sq. ft. 
  * 2,500 sq. ft. 
  * 3,000 sq. ft. 
  * 3,500 sq. ft. 
  * 4,000 sq. ft. 
  * 4,500 sq. ft. 
  * 5,000 sq. ft. 
  * 5,500 sq. ft. 
  * 6,000 sq. ft. 
  * 6,500 sq. ft. 
  * 7,000 sq. ft. 
  * 7,500 sq. ft. 
  * 8,000 sq. ft. 
  * 8,500 sq. ft. 
  * 9,000 sq. ft. 
  * 9,500 sq. ft. 
  * 10,000 sq. ft. 
  * 10,500 sq. ft. 
  * 11,000 sq. ft. 
  * 11,500 sq. ft. 
  * 12,000 sq. ft. 
  * 12,500 sq. ft. 
  * 13,000 sq. ft. 
  * 13,500 sq. ft. 
  * 14,000 sq. ft. 
  * 14,500 sq. ft. 
  * 15,000 sq. ft. 
  * 15,500 sq. ft. 
  * 16,000 sq. ft. 
  * 16,500 sq. ft. 
  * 17,000 sq. ft. 
  * 17,500 sq. ft. 
  * 18,000 sq. ft. 
  * 18,500 sq. ft. 
  * 19,000 sq. ft. 
  * 19,500 sq. ft. 
  * 20,000 sq. ft. 

__Clear

__Advanced Search

**JRD Group DMCC  \- Website Privacy Policy for all websites owned and operated by JRD Group DMCC. Updated: 15th August 2016**

This Privacy Policy (the “ **Policy** ”) sets out the basis on which **JRD Group DMCC**  collects, uses and discloses personal information obtained from you when using [www.justrentals.com](http://www.justrentals.com/), [www.propspace.com](http://www.propspace.com/), [www.justproperty.com](http://www.justproperty.com/) and/or [www.jrdgroup.com](http://www.jrdgroup.com/) (the “ **Website(s)** ”).

By visiting the Website(s) and/or by using any services provided via the Website(s), you expressly agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy and you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your information in accordance with the terms of this Policy. We may amend this Policy at any time without notice. If you do not agree to the Policy (including any amendments), then you should immediately cease using the Website.

**Your Information**

The type of information we collect from you is either personal to you, or is general in nature:

  * **Personal Information** : When you register on the Website as a customer, update your information, purchase any goods or services, take part in promotions or send emails to us, you provide us with information that we store and process. Such information may include your name, address, phone number, email address, purchase and transaction history, billing information (including credit card information), interests, and other such 'Personal Information'.
  * **General Information** : We may also receive more general information from you as a result of your visits to, and use of, the Website. This general information does not identify you personally, and can include information such as your IP address, the date and time you access the Website, length of time you spend on the Website, your browsing history (recorded by the text and graphics files that compose that page), the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Website, and other such 'General Information'.

**Collecting and Using Information**

Most of this Website can be used without giving us any information. However, certain services may involve collection of information from you. We use this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular to: keep internal records; improve our products, services and the Websites; communicate with you if you have ordered or purchased products from us; contact you for market research purposes; and provide you with information about new products, promotions, special offers and other information.

We use Personal Information for a range of business-related purposes, including: account registration (eg. your name, telephone number and email address); billing information, transaction and credit card information (should you make a purchase with us); and information regarding your interests, demographics, experiences and contact preferences in order to provide you with further correspondence about our products and services. If you contact us via the Website, or via email to the contacts set out on the Website, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

We use General Information to help us make the Website more useful to visitors (including to help us assess content of interest to visitors), and for other purposes such as determining the Website’s technical design specifications and identifying system performance or problem areas, for tracking activity on the Website, preparing reports, assessing trends, and otherwise monitoring the way in which the Website is being used – none of which would be in a way that personally identifies any users.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

You agree that we may share your Personal Information within the JRD Group of companies. We may provide your Personal Information in any manner to any third parties outside the JRD Group of Companies for marketing or third party promotion purposes; or if required to do so by law or any governing authority; or to protect our own legitimate interests.

**Security**

Keeping your Personal Information secure and preventing unauthorized access is of utmost priority to us, and we take all steps reasonably necessary to protect your Personal Information against any unauthorised access, use, alteration, disclosure or destruction. Whilst we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to secure and safeguard your Personal Information, we will not be held responsible for any unauthorised access by third parties and we cannot guarantee that the Personal Information provided by you or that is transmitted via this Website or by e-mail is totally secure and safe.

**Cookies**

The Website uses cookies, which are files that store information on your hard drive that allow a website to recognize users, track new users and to record session information. This information is collected though Google Analytics and by using these Websites, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but if you choose you can disable the cookies from your browser. 

**Application Law and Jurisdiction**

This Policy, as well as your access to the Website, is subject to and governed by the laws of the United Arab Emirates as applied in the Emirate of Dubai without giving effect to conflicts of law principles thereof. Any dispute regarding this Policy or our handling of your Personal Information and General Information shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts in Dubai.

**Contact Us**

If you have any queries, complaints or recommendations about this Policy, or if you believe that any Personal Information that we may hold about you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at the following address and we will endeavor to respond to you promptly.
